seacoastbank.com 2010-04-15

# FACTS

                                                                                                                                     Rev. 3/2010
                               WHAT DOES SEACOAST DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 FACTS
 Why?                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                               the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                               share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we
                               do.
 What?                         The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                               with us. This information can include:
                                 l Social Security number                               l Credit history
                                 l Payment history                                      l Account transactions
                                 l Transaction history                                  l Checking account information
 How?                          All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business.
                               In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal
                               information; the reasons Seacoast chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
    Reasons we can share your personal information                           Does Seacoast share?               Can you limit this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes -                                                     Yes                              No
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your
 account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes -                                                             Yes                              No
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                       Yes                              No
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                         Yes                              No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                         No                          We don't share
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                      Yes                              Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                       No                          We don't share
 To limit our                    l Call Toll-free 866-674-5578 then select option 7 - our menu will prompt you through your
 sharing                       choice(s)
                               Please note:
                               If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
                               notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in
                               this notice.
                               However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?                    Call toll-free 800-706-9991
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                       PRIV-MODEL 3/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                                         2010.1/0643 2287663-010 CUSTOM                         Page 1 of 2

 Page 2
 Who We Are
 Who is providing this notice?           Seacoast means the following institutions: Seacoast National Bank and FNB
                                         Brokerage Services, Inc.
 What We Do
 How does Seacoast protect my            To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
 personal information?                   security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
                                         safeguards and secured files and buildings.
 How does Seacoast collect my            We collect your personal information, for example, when you
 personal information?                     l Open an account                                 l Apply for financing
                                           l Apply for a loan                                l Give us your contact information
                                           l Seek advice about your investments
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                         affiliates, or other companies.
 Why can't I limit all sharing?          Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                           l sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your
                                              creditworthiness
                                           l affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                           l sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                         See below for more on your rights under state law.
 What happens when I limit               If you have obtained a product or service jointly with another person or persons,
 sharing for an account I hold           you will be given the opportunity to limit marketing just to yourself, or you may
 jointly with someone else?              limit marketing to all parties to the account. Note: You will be required to enter the
                                         social security number of each individual separately that you wish to limit
                                         marketing offers.
 Definitions
 Affiliates                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                         non-financial companies.
                                           l Our affiliates include:
                                               l Seacoast National Bank
                                               l FNB Brokerage Services, Inc.
 Nonaffiliates                           Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                         non-financial companies.
                                           l Seacoast does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
 Joint Marketing                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                         financial products or services to you.
                                           l Our joint marketing partners include our credit card partner
 Other Important Information
 For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Customers. We will not share personal information with
 nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
 For California Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you
 or for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you
 with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
 For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Customers. We will not share personal information from deposit or
 share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
 For Vermont Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or
 for joint marketing without your authorization, and we will not share personal information with affiliates about your
 creditworthiness without your authorization.
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                               PRIV-MODEL 3/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                                 2010.1/0643 2287663-010 CUSTOM                        Page 2 of 2
